<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Euro Diaries 24 - The Sequel</title>
    <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Euro Diaries 24 - The Sequel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Belgium Squad</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/belgium-squad-reaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/belgium-squad-reaction/</guid>
      
      <description>Belgium Squad Reaction A new era begins after the departure of Roberto Martinez after the World Cup(Ranted way too hard about him in the World Cup Post) but he&amp;rsquo;s in Portugal. He better not mess up Ronaldo&amp;rsquo;s 6th Euros or we will have words AGAIN. Anyways let&amp;rsquo;s see what Tedesco has picked for this Belgium team
Goalkeeper A major miss here which you could see is the exclusion of Thibaut Courtois.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Germany Squad</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/germany-squad-reaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:40:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/germany-squad-reaction/</guid>
      
      <description>Germany Squad Reaction These guys man. Went under the radar so much given how they underperformed and went out in one CRAZY group in the World Cup but honestly they&amp;rsquo;ve now looked much better honestly, and they&amp;rsquo;ve got a returnee from retirement, and you&amp;rsquo;re looking at him in the image. Yep Toni Kroos announced his return to international duty for this tournament. Fresh off winning the Champions League with Real Madrid and announcing his retirement in club football, he&amp;rsquo;s got a point to prove and I hope his mentality will carry Germany through this tournament because they&amp;rsquo;re the hosts this time.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>France Squad</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/france-squad-reaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:40:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/france-squad-reaction/</guid>
      
      <description>France Squad Reaction World Cup finalists. Absolutely one of the favorites. They have a strong squad headed by new Real Madrid recruit Kylian Mbappé. Let&amp;rsquo;s get into it
Goalkeeper You&amp;rsquo;ve got 2 great options in Mike Maignan and Alphonse Areola who have had good seasons for their respective clubs, but I don&amp;rsquo;t think you can look past Maignan for this spot, and I&amp;rsquo;d go for him too
Defense We&amp;rsquo;re looking at a new generation of defenders after Varane announced his retirement from internation football after the World Cup 2 years ago.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portugal Squad</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/portugal-squad-reaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 18:40:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/portugal-squad-reaction/</guid>
      
      <description>Portugal Squad Reaction Alright. Former Euro winners. Quite possibly the last dance from Ronaldo in a major tournament, and also Pepe too. Knowing Ronaldo, he&amp;rsquo;ll want to be there for 2 more years for the World Cup, but I think it&amp;rsquo;s a stretch even for him. I&amp;rsquo;ll respect it, but I feel he&amp;rsquo;ll have not been as good as he is relative to now. And also I have no trust in Roberto Martinez at all given what he ruined with Belgium.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spain Squad</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/spain-squad-reaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 18:40:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/spain-squad-reaction/</guid>
      
      <description>Spain Squad Reaction Alright. Got some good talent here and experience too. They&amp;rsquo;re in a group with Italy and Croatia, so it&amp;rsquo;s going to be tough. Let&amp;rsquo;s go through each of them for this 4-3-3 formation that they&amp;rsquo;re obviously going to go with
Goalkeeper I think this is a nailed on pick. David Raya. Fantastic debut season with the Golden Glove with Arsenal in the Premier League. The quality of the others are good as well with Unai Simon and Alex Remiro, but Raya is definitely a shoo in.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy Squad</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/italy-provisional-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 18:40:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/italy-provisional-squad/</guid>
      
      <description>Italy Provisional Squad The major news here is Scalvini might miss this tournament because of a major injury he just got recently
Alright. The defending champions of the Euros. It is hard to gauge them because they actually FAILED to qualify for the World Cup 2 years back but they&amp;rsquo;ve got some good players now and some good young talents as well. And as always you&amp;rsquo;ve got Fede Chiesa as well involved too.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>England Squad</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/england-provisional-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 18:40:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/england-provisional-squad/</guid>
      
      <description>England Provisional Squad I&amp;rsquo;ll be reacting to all the available squads till now and add the final squad once it&amp;rsquo;s announced in the same page.
Starting with England. Probably the biggest favorites to win this tournament which isn&amp;rsquo;t a surprise given the talent they&amp;rsquo;ve got and with this squad it shows. The only gripe I have is the man behind them: Yes I mean Boregate. Because honestly for the talent they have they&amp;rsquo;ve got probably the worst ever coach to lead it.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Euro 2024 - Groups</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 18:40:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/groups/</guid>
      
      <description></description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Euro 2024 Duration</title>
      <link>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/duration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 18:40:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlescsr.github.io/euro-diaries-24/posts/duration/</guid>
      
      <description>15th June 2024 - 15th July 2024</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
